Guide to the Helen and Newton Harrison Papers M1797
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 14. Public Relations Material, 1961-2010
  - Subseries 1. Harrisons, 1961-2009
    - Waterfront Project: A Public Forum, San Francisco Art Institute, San Francisco, CA, 1977 (Box 198, Folder 10)
    - Artists Investigate the Environment, Municipal Art Gallery, Los Angeles, CA, 1978 (Flat-box 279, Folder 29)
    - From the Lagoon Cycle; From the Meditations, Portland Center for the Visual Arts, Portland OR, 1978 (Box 198, Folder 11)
    - Big San Diego Show, Newspace Gallery, Los Angeles, CA, 1978 (Box 198, Folder 12)
    - Technology and the Great Lakes, the Gentle Art of Survival, Charles Allis Art Library, Milwaukee, WI, 1978 (Box 198, Folder 13)
    - Social Works, Los Angeles Institute of Contemporary Art, Los Angeles, CA, 1979 (Box 198, Folder 14)
    - Art as Social Paradigm, Berry College, Mt. Berry, GA, 1979 (Box 198, Folder 15)
    - Custom and Culture: A Series of Free Arts Events, New York City, NY, 1979 (Box 198, Folder 16)
    - Dialogue / Discourse / Research, Santa Barbara Museum of Art, Santa Barbara, CA, 1979 (Box 198, Folder 17)
    - Helen and Newton Harrison at Claremont, Claremont Graduate School, Libra Gallery, Claremont, CA, 1979 (Box 198, Folder 18)
    - SITE: Sculptors and Landscape Architects Exploring Interdisciplinary Alternatives in Environmental Design, Minneapolis College of Art and Design, Minneapolis, MN, 1979 (Flat-box 279, Folder 30)
    - American Women Artists 1980, Museu de Arte Contemporânea da Universidade de São Paulo, São Paulo, Brazil (Box 198, Folder 19)
    - American Women Artists 1980, Museu de Arte Contemporânea da Universidade de São Paulo, São Paulo, Brazil (Flat-box 279, Folder 31)
    - Contemporary Art in Southern California, The High Museum, Atlanta, GA, 1980 (Flat-box 270, Folder 25)
    - One Grand Leap Year Art Sale, Franklin furnace, New York City, NY, 1980 (Box 198, Folder 20)
    - "Sculpture and Land Reclamation," The 11th International Sculpture Conference, Washington, D.C., 1980 (Box 198, Folder 21)
    - Talking Water, Ronald Feldman Fine Arts, New York City, NY, 1980 (Flat-box 270, Folder 26)
    - UC Faculty Art Exhibition, Mandeville Art Gallery, University of California, San Diego, San Diego, CA, 1980 (Box 198, Folder 22)
    - Baltimore Promenade, Maryland Institute College of Art, Baltimore, MD, 1981 (Box 198, Folder 23)
    - California: The State of Landscape 1872-1981, Newport Harbor Art Museum, Newport Beach, CA (Box 198, Folder 24)
    - Heresies, The Grey Art Gallery, New York City, NY, 1981 (Box 198, Folder 25)
    - Équinoxe 80, Centre Georges Pompidou, Musée National d'Art Moderne, Paris, France, 1981 (Box 198, Folder 26)
    - Woman's Building, Los Angeles, CA, 1981 (Box 198, Folder 27)
      A slide lecture by Helen Harrison and Kathy Arnold.
    - On the Environment II: Two Days Co-Sponsored by the Center for Music Experiment, Sushi: A Performance Gallery, and Landmark Art Projects, San Diego, CA, 1982 (Box 198, Folder 28)
    - Baltimore Promenade, Decker Gallery, Maryland Institute College of Art, Baltimore, MD, 1982 (Flat-box 279, Folder 32)
    - Baltimore Promenade, Washington Project for the Arts, Washington, D.C., 1982 (Box 198, Folder 29)
    - Common Ground: Five Artists in the Florida Landscape, Ringling Museum, Sarasota, FL, 1982 (Box 198, Folder 30)
    - Environmental Narratives, Ronald Feldman Fine Arts, New York City, NY, 1982 (Box 198, Folder 31)
    - Environmental Narratives, Ronald Feldman Fine Arts, New York City, NY, 1982 (Map-folder 473)
    - Barrier Island Drama: The Mangrove and the Pine, Wenger Gallery, San Diego, CA, 1983 (Box 198, Folder 32)
    - Guadalupe Meander, A Refugia for San Jose, San Jose Museum of Art, San Jose, CA, 1983 (Flat-box 279, Folder 33)
    - The Mangrove & the Pine and Three Urban Projects, University of Texas, Arlington, Arlington, TX, 1983 (Flat-box 279, Folder 34)
    - "Words of Wisdom," Artist Lecture Series '83, San Jose State University, San Jose, CA, 1983 (Box 198, Folder 33)
    - "Words of Wisdom," Artist lecture series '83, San Jose State University, San Jose, CA, 1983 (Map-folder 474)
    - Content: A Contemporary Focus, 1974-1984, The Hirshhorn Museum, Washington, D.C. (Box 198, Folder 34)
    - Destroyed Print, Eve Drewelowe Gallery, University of Colorado Art Galleries, Boulder, CO, 1984 (Box 198, Folder 35)
    - Disarming Images: Art for Nuclear Disarmament, The Contemporary Arts Center, Cincinnati, OH, 1984 (Box 198, Folder 36)
    - Disarming Images: Art for Nuclear Disarmament, University Art Gallery, San Diego State University, 1984 (Map-folder 475)
    - Landmarks, Edith Blum Art Gallery, Bard College, Annandale-on-Hudson, NY, 1984 (Flat-box 279, Folder 35)
    - Revolutions Per Minute (The Art Record), California State University, Northridge, CA, 1984 (Box 198, Folder 37)
    - Disarming Images (The Shadow of the Bomb), 1984 (Map-folder 398)
    - Unique Works on Paper, Wenger Gallery, San Diego, CA, 1984 (Box 198, Folder 38)
    - University of California, San Diego Faculty Art Exhibition 1984, Mandeville Art Gallery, San Diego, CA (Flat-box 277, Folder 23)
    - 1+1= 2: An Exhibition of 33 Husband and Wife Couples, Traveling exhibition, 1984-1985 (Box 198, Folder 39)
      Bernice Steinbaum Gallery, New York City, NY; Boca Raton Museum of Arts, Boca Raton, FL; University of California, Davis, Davis, CA
    - Arroyo Seco Release / Serpentine for Pasadena, Baxter Art Gallery, California Institute of Technology, Pasadena, CA, 1985 (Flat-box 279, Folder 36)
    - Artist as Social Designer: Aspects of Public Urban Art Today, Los Angeles County Museum of Art, 1985 (Flat-box 279, Folder 37)
    - Focus Environment, Harrisons show the Guadalupe Meander: A Refugia for San Jose, Fine Arts Gallery, University of California, Irvine, Irvine, CA, 1985 (Flat-box 277, Folder 24)
    - Baltimore Promenade: An Environmental Project, Wenger Gallery, La Jolla, CA, 1985 (Box 198, Folder 40)
    - Four Urban Projects, Tortue Gallery, Santa Monica, CA, 1985 (Box 198, Folder 41)
    - The Lagoon Cycle, Johnson Museum, Cornell University, Ithaca, NY, 1985 (Box 198, Folder 42)
      Mailers kept for addresses.
    - The Lagoon Cycle, Johnson Museum, Cornell University, Ithaca, NY, 1985 (Map-folder 399)
    - The Lagoon Cycle, Johnson Museum, Cornell University, Ithaca, NY, 1985 (Flat-box 277, Folder 25)
    - Sixteen x Twenty-Six Landscapes, Quint Gallery, San Diego, CA, 1985 (Box 198, Folder 43)
    - A Tale of Three Cities, Ronald Feldman Fine Arts, New York City, NY, 1985 (Box 198, Folder 44)
    - "To the Astonishing Horizon: New Approaches to Landscape in Southern California," The Design Center of Los Angeles, Los Angeles, CA, 1985 (Box 198, Folder 45)
    - "Art and Public Art: Art in the Public Interest," University of New Mexico, Albuquerque, NM, 1986 (Box 198, Folder 46)
    - A Benefit for the Del Mar Communications Center, Del Mar, CA, 1986 (Box 198, Folder 47)
    - Disarming Images: Art for Nuclear Disarmament, Traveling exhibition, 1986 (Box 198, Folder 48)
      The Bronx Museum of Art, Bronx, NY; University of California, Irvine, Irvine, CA; The University of Nevada, Las Vegas, Las Vegas, NV
    - Guadaloupe Meander: A Refugia for San Jose, Palomar College, San Marcos, CA, 1986 (Box 198, Folder 49)
    - New Public Art: Toward Understanding, Civic Garden Center, Dallas, TX, 1986 (Box 198, Folder 50)
    - Weep for Adonis: Old Heroes and New Villains, Culman Gouro Gallery, Los Angeles, CA, 1986 (Box 198, Folder 51)
    - With the Land: A Photographic Survey, Sonoma State University, Rohnert Park, CA, 1986 (Box 198, Folder 52)
    - With the Land: A Photographic Survey, Sonoma State University, Rohnert Park, CA, 1986 (Map-folder 476)
    - At Issue: Art and Advocacy, St. Louis Gallery of Contemporary Art, St. Louis, MO, 1987 (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - Book of the Seven Lagoons, University of Nevada, Las Vegas, Las Vegas, NV, 1987 (Box 199, Folder 2)
    - Helen & Newton Harrison, Wenger Gallery, Los Angeles, CA, 1987 (Box 199, Folder 3)
    - The Lagoon Cycle, Los Angeles County Museum of Art, Los Angeles, CA, 1987 (Box 199, Folder 4)
    - Nobody told us when to stop thinking..., The Grey Gallery, New York University, New York City, NY, 1987 (Box 199, Folder 5)
    - Nobody told us when to stop thinking..., The Grey Gallery, New York University, New York City, NY, 1987 (Flat-box 279, Folder 38)
    - SPE (Society for Photographic Education) Western Regional Conference, Morro Bay, CA, 1987 (Box 199, Folder 6)
    - Devil's Gate Transformation: A Refugia for Pasadena, Pasadena Gallery of Contemporary Arts, Pasadena, CA, 1987-1988 (Box 199, Folder 7)
    - Art for the Record: Issues of Documentation in Contemporary Art, Huntington Library and Art Gallery, San Marino, CA, 1988 (Box 199, Folder 8)
    - The Book of the Seven Lagoons, Traveling exhibition, 1988 (Box 199, Folder 9)
      CU Galleries, University of Colorado at Boulder, Boulder, CO; daadgalerie, Berlin, Germany
    - Diversity and Presence: Women Faculty Artists of the University of California, University of California, Santa Cruz, Santa Cruz, CA, 1988 (Box 199, Folder 10)
    - The Flower Show, Betsy Rosenfield Greenhouse, Inc., Chicago, IL, 1988 (Box 199, Folder 11)
    - Models and Drawings for Santa Barbara Sites, University Art Museum, University of California, Santa Barbara, Santa Barbara, CA, 1988 (Box 199, Folder 12)
    - Raw Material, Althea Viafora Gallery, New York City, NY, 1988 (Box 199, Folder 13)
    - UCSD Faculty Art '88, University of California, San Diego, San Diego, CA, 1988 (Box 199, Folder 14)
    - Visiting artists, University of Colorado, Boulder, Boulder, CO, 1988 (Map-folder 477)
    - Atempause für den Sava-Fluss, Neuer Berliner Kunstverein, Berlin, Germany, 1989 (Box 199, Folder 15)
    - Best of the Eighties, Exhibition and Auction, The Junior Council of the Laguna Art Museum, Laguna Beach, CA, 1989 (Box 199, Folder 16)
    - City Sites: Artists and Urban Strategies, California College of Arts and Crafts, Oakland, CA, 1989 (Box 199, Folder 17)
    - City Sites: Artists and Urban Strategies, California College of Arts and Crafts, Oakland, CA, 1989 (Flat-box 270, Folder 27)
    - Collecting / Organizing / Transposing, Maryland Art Place, Baltimore, MD, 1989 (Box 199, Folder 18)
    - A Day Without Art, University of California, San Diego, San Diego, CA, 1989 (Box 199, Folder 19)
    - The Drowned World: Waterworks, Tangeman Fine Arts Gallery, University of Cincinnati, Cincinnati, OH, 1989 (Box 199, Folder 20)
    - The End Of The Weather As We Know It, Randolph Street Gallery, Chicago, IL, 1989 (Box 199, Folder 21)
    - OFF-SITE: Artists in Response to the Environment, Richmond Art Center, Richmond, CA, 1989 (Box 199, Folder 22)
    - Sava River, 1989 (Map-folder 400)
    - OFF-SITE: Artists in Response to the Environment, Richmond Art Center, Richmond, CA, 1989 (Flat-box 277, Folder 26)
    - Smarts Festival, Pico Seagate Exhibition, Santa Monica, CA, 1989 (Box 199, Folder 23)
    - The Unconventional Landscape, John Michael Kohler Arts Center, Sheboygan, WI, 1989 (Box 199, Folder 24)
    - Vesta Awards: Honoring women who have made significant contributions to the arts in Southern California, Woman's Building, Los Angeles, CA, 1989 (Box 199, Folder 25)
    - Women's Caucus for Art: "Bridging the Gaps," National Conference, San Francisco, CA, 1989 (Box 199, Folder 26)
    - The Works of Helen and Newton Harrison, Laguna Art Museum, Laguna Beach, CA, 1989 (Box 199, Folder 27)
    - "The Map is Not the Territory," Mid-America College Art Conference, University of Cincinnati, Cincinnati, OH, 1989 (Box 199, Folder 28)
    - "The Map is Not the Territory," Mid America College Art Conference, University of Cincinnati, Cincinnati, OH, 1989 (Map-folder 478)
    - Artists' Garden Weimar, Bauhaus-University Weimar, Germany, circa 1990 (Box 199, Folder 29)
    - Art Contemporain 1990: Savoir-vivre, Savoir-faire, Savoir-être, Montréal, Canada (Box 199, Folder 30)
    - Arts Revue '89, Artvision 1990, Channel 10, Manhattan Beach, CA (Box 199, Folder 31)
      Video art series
    - Biodiversity and Landscapes: Human Challenges for Conservation in the Changing World, Center For BioDiversity Research, Environmental Resources Research Institute, Pennsylvania State University, University Park, PA, 1990 (Box 199, Folder 32)
    - The Book of the Seven Lagoons, Kunstverein, Hamburg, Germany, 1990 (Box 199, Folder 33)
    - Breathing Space for the Sava River, Traveling exhibition, 1990 (Box 199, Folder 34)
      Moderna Galerija, Ljubljana, Slovenia; Muzeja revolucije naroda Hrvatske, Zagreb, Yugoslavia
    - Construction in Process: back in Łódź 1990, History Museum of Łódź, Poland (Box 199, Folder 35)
    - Devil’s Gate Transformation / A Refuge for Pasadena, The Armory Center for the Arts, Pasadena, CA, 1990 (Box 199, Folder 36)
    - Direct Descendants, Self-Help Graphics, Galería Otra Vez, Los Angeles, CA, 1990 (Box 199, Folder 37)
    - Environmental Art with Helen Mayer Harrison and Newton Harrison, Winter 1990 Cultural Art Series, Jewish Community Center (JCC), La Jolla, CA (Box 199, Folder 38)
    - In Situ: The Dynamics of Public Art in Southern California, California State University, Long Beach, Long Beach, CA, 1990 (Box 199, Folder 39)
    - International Sculpture '90, International Sculpture Symposium, Washington, D.C., 1990 (Box 199, Folder 40)
    - Polemical Landscapes, California Museum of Photography, University of California, Riverside, Riverside, CA, 1990 (Box 199, Folder 41)
    - Signs of Life, Institute of Contemporary Art, University of Pennsylvania, Philadelphia, PA, 1990 (Box 199, Folder 42)
    - Terra Incognita: New Directions in Contemporary Landscape, The Rhode Island School of Design Museum of Art, Providence, RI, 1990 (Box 199, Folder 43)
    - Concept / Object, Wenger Gallery, Los Angeles, CA, 1990-1991 (Box 199, Folder 44)
    - Revered Earth, Traveling exhibition, 1990-1991 (Box 199, Folder 45)
      Contemporary Arts Museum, Houston, Houston, TX; Center for Contemporary Arts Santa Fe, Santa Fe, NM; University of Arizona Museum of Art, Arizona, AZ
    - Artists Contributing to the Solution, The Woman's Building, Los Angeles, CA, 1991 (Box 199, Folder 46)
    - Changing the Conversation, Ronald Feldman Fine Arts, New York City, NY, 1991 (Box 199, Folder 47)
    - Conversational Drift, Installation Gallery, San Diego, CA, 1991 (Box 199, Folder 48)
    - Des Artistes Aux Ateliers D'été de Cergy, Cergy-Pontoise, France, 1991 (Box 199, Folder 49)
    - "Design Talks," Parsons School of Design, New York City, NY, 1991 (Flat-box 279, Folder 39)
    - East meets West: The Arts and the Environment, Traveling Exhibition, 1991 (Box 199, Folder 50)
    - Mapping the Terrain: The New Public Art, California College of Arts and Crafts, Oakland, CA, 1991 (Box 199, Folder 51)
    - Team Spirit, Cleveland Center for Contemporary Art, Cleveland, OH, 1991 (Box 199, Folder 52)
    - Beyond Outer Spaces: Environments We Can Live With, C.C.A.S.L.A. Conference '92, Santa Barbara, CA, 1992 (Box 199, Folder 53)
      California Council of American Society of Landscape Architects
    - California Artists' Books, Armory Center for the Arts, Pasadena, CA, 1992 (Box 200, Folder 1)
    - Changing the Conversation: Environmental Projects Proposed and in Progress, Washington University Gallery of Art, St. Louis, MO, 1992 (Box 200, Folder 2)
    - Exploring Maps, Turman Art Gallery, Indiana State University, Terre Haute, IN, 1992 (Box 200, Folder 3)
    - "The Forum Goes Out into the Garden…and Beyond," Los Angeles, CA, 1992 (Flat-box 270, Folder 28)
    - Fragile Ecologies: Contemporary Artists' Interpretations and Solutions, The Queens Museum of Art, Queens, NY, 1992 (Box 200, Folder 4)
    - Imperiled Shores, The Baxter Gallery, Portland School of Art, Portland, ME, 1992 (Box 200, Folder 5)
    - Michael M. Williamson Memorial Lecture, Helen and Newton Harrison, Indiana State University, Terre Haute, IN, 1992 (Box 200, Folder 6)
    - Reinventing Nature: Ecological Art and Social Responsibility, University of California Humanities Research Institute, Irvine, CA, 1992 (Box 200, Folder 7)
    - A Residency by Helen Mayer Harrison and Newton Harrison, 1992 (Box 200, Folder 8)
      Raleigh and Durham, NC
    - Revered Earth, Mint Museum, Charlotte, NC, 1992 (Box 200, Folder 9)
    - Site Seeing, Islip Art Museum, East Islip, NY, 1992 (Box 200, Folder 10)
    - UC San Diego Faculty Exhibition, Mandeville Gallery, University of California, San Diego, La Jolla, CA, 1992 (Box 200, Folder 11)
    - Art and the Environment, Allegheny College, Meadville, PA, 1993 (Flat-box 277, Folder 27)
    - Artists: Key Players in Environmental Solutions, The Evergreen State College, Olympia, WA, 1993 (Box 200, Folder 12)
    - Book of the Seven Lagoons, Washington University Gallery of Art, St. Louis, MO, 1993 (Box 200, Folder 13)
    - Creative Solutions to Ecological Issues, Dallas Museum of Natural History, Dallas, TX, 1993 (Box 200, Folder 14)
    - Fragile Ecologies: Contemporary Artists' Interpretations and Solutions, San Jose Museum of Art, San Jose, CA, 1993 (Box 200, Folder 15)
    - Fragile Ecologies, Madison Art Center, Madison, WI, 1993 (Map-folder 479)
    - Kunst, Kultur, Ökologie, Akademie der Bildenden Künste München, Munich, Germany, 1993 (Box 200, Folder 16)
    - Kunst-Kultur-Ökologie, Bea Voigt Galerie, Munich, Germany, 1993 (Flat-box 277, Folder 28)
    - Recent Environmental Projects, Floria/Brown Gallery, Woody Creek, CO, 1993 (Box 200, Folder 17)
    - San Diego Artists from the Collection of the Museum of Contemporary Art, Boehm Gallery, Palomar, CA, 1993 (Box 200, Folder 18)
    - The Serpentine Lattice, Reed College, Portland, OR, 1993 (Box 200, Folder 19)
      First version
    - The Serpentine Lattice, Ronald Feldman Fine Arts, New York City, NY, 1993 (Box 200, Folder 20)
      Second version
    - Generations of Mentors, Mount St. Mary's College, Los Angeles, CA, 1995 (Box 200, Folder 21)
    - A Green Heart Vision, Kunstcentrum Burgvliet, Gouda, Holland, 1995 (Box 200, Folder 22)
    - Green Piece: Contemporary Art Dealing with Modern Issues Facing Modern Society, Castle Gallery, College of New Rochelle, New Rochelle, NY, 1995 (Box 200, Folder 23)
    - Het Groene Hart, Centrum Beeldende Kunst, Leiden, Holland, 1995 (Box 200, Folder 24)
    - Kunst und Ökologie: Rekultivierung von Landschaften, München, Germany, 1995 (Box 200, Folder 25)
    - Scavare Il Futuro: Arte, natura e cultura tra la Sardegna e l'Europa, Cagliari, Sardinia, 1995 (Box 200, Folder 26)
    - UCSD Visual Arts Faculty Exhibition, University California, San Diego, La Jolla, CA, 1995 (Box 200, Folder 27)
    - The Edge of Town, Joseloff Gallery at the University of Hartford, West Hartford, CT, 1995-1996 (Box 200, Folder 28)
    - The Edge of Town, Joseloff Gallery at the University of Hartford, West Hartford, CT, 1995-1996 (Map-folder 480)
    - California Wash: A Memorial, Pico-Seagate, Santa Monica, CA, 1996 (Box 200, Folder 29)
    - California Wash: A Memorial, Pico-Seagate, Santa Monica, CA, 1996 (Flat-box 277, Folder 29)
    - Ein Braunkohlepark für den Südraum Leipzig, Bonn Germany, 1996 (Box 200, Folder 30)
    - Future Garden, Teil 1: Die gefährdeten Wiesen Europas, Kunst- und Ausstellungshalle der Bundesrepublik Deutschland, Bonn, Germany, 1996 (Box 200, Folder 31)
    - Ropes, Rings, Lattices, and Lace - Retrofitting Biodiversity into Cultural Landscape, University of Bonn, Bonn, Germany, 1996 (Flat-box 279, Folder 40)
    - Villette-Amazone: Manifeste pour l'environnement au XXI siècle, La Villette, Paris, France, 1996 (Box 200, Folder 32)
    - "Wasser, Erde, Luft: Reflexionen über die Stillegung des Tagebaus in Sachsen-Anhalt und Sachsenemph," Architektur-Biennale Venedig, 1996 (Box 200, Folder 33)
    - Future Garden, Kunst- und Ausstellungshalle der Bundesrepublik Deutschland, Bonn, Germany, 1996-1998 (Box 200, Folder 34)
    - "Ropes, Rings, Lattices, and Lace," PG&E Energy Center, San Francisco, CA, 1997 (Flat-box 270, Folder 29)
    - UCSD Visual Arts 30th Anniversary Faculty Exhibition, University California, San Diego, La Jolla, CA, 1997 (Box 200, Folder 35)
    - Aufriss: Künstlerische Positionen zur Industrielandschaft in der Mitte Europas, Brandenburgischen Kunstsammlungen Cottbus, Cottbus, Germany, 1997-1998 (Box 200, Folder 36)
    - Casting a Green Net: Can it Be We are Seeing a Dragon?, Artranspennine 98: An Exhibition of International Contemporary Visual Art, Liverpool, England, 1998 (Box 200, Folder 37)
    - Casting a Green Net: Can it Be We are Seeing a Dragon?, Bluecoat Gallery, Liverpool, England, 1998 (Map-folder 481)
    - Helen and Newton Harrison, California State University, Stanislaus, Turlock, CA, 1998 (Box 200, Folder 38)
    - "On the Urgency of the Moment – Addressing the Cultural Landscape at Scale," Bauhaus University Weimar, Weimar, Germany, 1998 (Box 200, Folder 39)
    - A Place in the Sun: Visualizing LA Public Spaces, Armory Center for the Arts, Pasadena, CA, 1998 (Box 200, Folder 40)
    - Natural Reality: Kunstlerische Positionen zwischen Natur und Kultur, Ludwig Forum für Internationale Kunst, Aachen, Germany, 1999 (Box 200, Folder 41)
    - Expo 2000: Symposium 2000, Hannover, Germany (Box 200, Folder 42)
    - The Serpentine Lattice, Hatton Gallery, Colorado State University, Fort Collins, CO, 2000 (Box 200, Folder 43)
    - Peninsula Europa: The High Grounds, Altes Rathaus, Potsdam, Germany, 2001 (Box 200, Folder 44)
    - Péninsule Europe, Les Abattoirs, Toulouse, France, 2001 (Box 200, Folder 45)
    - Symposium: Art and Ecology – Visions, Collaborations, Enactments, Potsdam, Germany, 2001 (Box 201, Folder 1)
    - Halbinsel Europa, Ludwig Forum für Internationale Kunst, Aachen, Germany, 2002 (Box 201, Folder 2)
    - Peninsula Europe, Centre d'art contemporain de Castres, Castres, France, 2002 (Box 201, Folder 3)
    - Péninsule Europe, Les Abattoirs, Toulouse, France, 2002 (Box 201, Folder 4)
    - Schiereiland Europa, Kasteel Groeneveld, Baarn, Netherlands, 2002 (Box 201, Folder 5)
    - "Biodiversity, drainage basins and climate change: Lowlands in Europe", Kasteel Groeneveld, Baarn, Netherlands, 2003 (Box 201, Folder 6)
    - Peninsula Europe, Ronald Feldman Fine Arts, New York, NY, 2003 (Box 201, Folder 7)
    - Fluid Vistas Flevoland #2, De Verbeelding: kunst landschap natuur / art landscape nature, 2004 (Box 201, Folder 8)
    - Greenhouse Britain, Ronald Feldman Fine Arts, New York, NY, 2008 (Box 201, Folder 9)
    - "Intervene! Interrupt! Rethinking Art as Social Practice," University of California, Santa Cruz, Santa Cruz, CA, 2008 (Box 201, Folder 10)
    - Pioneering Figures of Ecological Art: Helen and Newton Mayer Harrison, David Brower Center, Berkeley CA, 2009 (Box 201, Folder 11)
    - Artists Work Here II: Performance Series, 424 "F" Street, San Diego, CA, undated (Box 201, Folder 12)
    - Colliding Fronts: Art & Science, N.A.M.E. Gallery, Chicago, IL, undated (Box 201, Folder 13)
    - Knock Out Visiting Artist Program, San Jose State University, San Jose, CA, undated (Map-folder 482)
    - LAICA's Fantastic Christmas & Chanuka Sale, Los Angeles Institute of Contemporary Art, Los Angeles, CA, undated (Box 201, Folder 14)
    - Nobody Told Us When to Stop Thinking, poster, undated (Flat-box 277, Folder 30)
    - UCSD Visual Arts Department Faculty Show, Art Gallery, University of California, San Diego, La Jolla, CA, undated (Box 201, Folder 15)
  - Subseries 2. Other, 1968-2010
    This series consists of mailers, flyers, programs, posters, catalogs, and other forms of public relations material documenting the careers of the Harrisons’ colleagues. The subseries is arranged chronologically.